Whitney: Can I Be Me is a music, documentary film directed by Nick Broomfield.
The life and tragic death of Whitney Houston.
Self (archive footage), played by Whitney Houston.
Self - Whitney's Mother, played by Cissy Houston.
Self - Whitney and Bobby Brown's Daughter (archive
footage), played by Bobbi Kristina Brown.
Self (archive footage), played by Bobby Brown.
Self - Whitney's Closest Confidant (archive footage), played by Robyn Crawford.
Self (archive footage), played by John Russell Houston Jr..
Whitney: Can I Be Me is a 2017 British-American documentary film that was written,
co-produced by Nick Broomfield and directed by Broomfield and Rudi Dolezal.
The film's subject is the life and career of singer Whitney Houston.
The film explores themes of career, biography, addiction, drugs, family.